carlashes.com 2010-06-27

# Privacy Statement

Turbo Style Products, LLC  
PATENT PENDING

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**The Information We Collect:**  
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the CarLashes website. On some pages, you can request information about our services.

**The Use of Information:**  
We use the information you provide about yourself to contact you and answer any questions you have about our services. We do not share this information with outside parties. We may also use the information you submit online to occasionally provide you with information regarding offers and new services from CarLashes.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. These addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

**Our Commitment To Data Security:**   
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Accessing Or Correcting Your Information:**  
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**If you have any questions about our privacy policy, pleasecontact us.**

CARLASHES™ MAKE YOU SMILE!  
Trademark Carlashes™ owned by Robert Small, And Used By Permission  
Copyright (c) 2009, 2010 Robert Small, And Used by Permission  
PATENT PENDING

SISTER SITES:  

REFERENCE:  
CUTE EYELASHES FOR YOUR CAR, EYELASHES FOR YOUR VW BUG, EYELASHES FOR YOUR MINI COOPER, EYELASHES FOR   
YOUR SMART CAR, PORCHE EYE LASHES, EYELASHES FOR YOUR PORCHE, VW EYELASHES, VOLKSWAGEN EYELASHES, BUG EYELASHES, MINI COOPER EYELASHES , SMART CAR EYELASHES, EYELASHES FOR YOUR HEADLIGHTS

home | sitemap | contact us | order | privacy statement  
© Copyright 2010 Carlashes™, All Rights Reserved.
